<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Governances on Git Guild</title>
    <link>http://deginner.com/governance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Governances on Git Guild</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 18:47:16 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://deginner.com/governance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>governance</title>
      <link>http://deginner.com/governance/governance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 18:47:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deginner.com/governance/governance/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-guild-is-formed-upon-two-or-more-individuals-pgp-signing-of-a-charter-that-specifies-the-purpose-of-a-software-project-and-the-rules-that-govern-the-development-of-the-project-which-can-include-definitions-of-membership-roles-responsibilities-code-quality-standards-monetary-policy-etc:898e7f1ceacb493c024554f5a7c87bdf&#34;&gt;A guild is formed upon two or more individuals PGP signing of a Charter that specifies the purpose of a software project and the rules that govern the development of the project, which can include definitions of membership, roles, responsibilities, code quality standards, monetary policy, etc.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Git and PGP have been chosen as the basis for the workflow and cryptographic signatures respectivelybecause these technologies are already widely used in open source projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;dash.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Dash&lt;/a&gt; provides a powerful and flexible governance model to base Git Guild off of. Just like Dash masternodes, certain Guild members will be empowered by the network to perform jobs, cast votes on various issues, and may be eligible to recieve a portion of network fees in return. Just like Dash masternodes, it is recommended that these empowered members be required to put up some collateral and perform their duties consistently and in a peer-reviewable manner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the sake of simplicity, lets say that members are organized into a classic guild hierarchy of Apprentices, Journeymen and Masters. Any policy change authorized by the Constitution can require a supermajority (66%) of approval by one or more class of Guild members.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>